my-article-city.com 2012-05-11

# Privacy Policy | My Article City

Your privacy is important to My-article-city.com and we take our responsibility seriously to protect the data that you provide us in the normal course of interacting with our site. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit My-article-city.com and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on My-article-city.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

DoubleClick DART cookies We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Customer and Membership Information:**  
Customer account information and Membership account information that you provide (such as your email address, address, phone number, password etc.) is held in strict confidence and will not be sold or rented to 3rd parties, but will be used for the purposes of providing services described on this website.

**Email Privacy:**

  *     Email Newsletter & Email Alert Subscription Forms

My-article-city.com uses subscription forms for individuals to request information by subscribing to email newsletters and/or email alerts based on their categories of interest. We collect contact information (like your name and/or email address amoung other data) to provide you with the information that you requested. We do not sell or rent email addresses to any 3rd parties.

  *     Confirm OPT-IN

We provide confirm opt-in opportunities for any email list(s) that you choose to receive. We use your email address to confirm your subscription and validity of the provided email address. Your reply to this email is necessary for completing your subscription to any ArticleLib email list or newsletter. You can change the email address that you have subscribed or you can unsubscribe with the email address you’re currently subscribed with and then subscribe again with a new email address.

  *     Unsubscribe

You can unsubscribe/opt-out for any or all email lists that you previously chose to receive. Emails sent to you includes the information necessary for removal from the list.

  *     User/Member/Client Communications

When you send email or other communications to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your requests and improve the quality of our services.

  *     Transactional Relationships

Customers, Members, and/or Users are considered to be engaged in a transactional relationship with My-article-city.com and as such, we may need to email or communicate with you from time to time in order to deliver our services.  
**Personal Information and Other Data We Collect:**

My-article-city.com collects personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, phone numbers, etc. when you register for various services we provide (example: Creating a membership account). We may combine this data with other My-article-city.com services or 3rd party data to provide a better user experience for you.  
My-article-city.com uses cookies (a piece of data stored on the user’s computer) and other technologies to provide you with a quality experience and to learn how you use our services so that we can continually innovate to improve our services.  
My-article-city.com servers may record/log information automatically any time you interact with our site or use any of our products & services. This may include information such as your IP address, URL, browser type, domain name(s), access dates & times, operating system, country of origin, language type, page views and user sessions to help diagnose problems and/or deliver our services to you.

**Uses:**

  * We may use the personal information you provided to provide the services you requested and for our own research and analysis to operate and improve on the services and products that we deliver, as well as develop new services and products.
  * We may share the aggregated non-personal information with 3rd parties outside of My-article-city.com.
  * When we use 3rd parties to assist us in the processing of your personal information (example: shopping cart service provider), we require that they comply with our Privacy Policies, confidentiality and security measures.
  * We may share information with 3rd parties in limited circumstances when complying with legal process, preventing suspected fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.
  * We may use your postal and electronic address to send you items and/or information relevant to your use of our services.
  * We may conduct member and/or user survey’s in order to improve our services.

**Links:**

This site contains links to other 3rd party sites and these sites are not covered under our privacy policy. We have made attempts to make sure these links are currently active but do not assure any responsibility for the content of these websites. We highly recommend that you review the privacy policies of these websites as well.  
My-article-city.com may present links in a way that allows us to track whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our services.

**Advertising Specific Terms & Conditions:**  
We use a combination of internal and 3rd party advertising companies to serve our ads on our website and in our emails, based on personal information. To track the effectiveness of the ads and provide a better user experience, these companies use information about your web visits to our website to serve relevant ads. Information collected and used may include IP address, geographical location, their cookie and and historical data previously collected. We will not provide any personal information to our advertisers when you interact with or view a targeted ad, however, by viewing or interacting with an ad, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will assume you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad(s).

**Security Management and Data Security:**  
The My-article-city.com web site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, including management procedures and specialized training for those who work directly with our databases. We take measures to protect against the unauthorized access of personal data, including physical security considerations of the stored data. We restrict access to personal data to My-article-city.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, innovate, and deliver our services.

**My-article-city.com Affiliate Partner Information:**  
All My-article-city.com affiliate information including address, phone number, email addresses, and tax id numbers are held in strict confidence. This information is collected for the purpose of generating commission payments, meeting United States federal tax laws, and managing our services.

**Notification of Changes:**  
From time to time, My-article-city.com will occasionally update our Privacy Policy. If there are any material changes to how we use your personal information, we will notify via email and provide you the opportunity to opt-out prior to any substantial change that has been taken. However, if you have opted out of all communication from My-article-city.com you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. My-article-city.com encourages you to periodically review our privacy policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your privacy.

**Your Choice:**  
You can decline to submit personal information for any of our services, in which case My-article-city.com may not be able to provide services to you.

**Legal Disclaimer:**  
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our web site or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Contacting this Web Site:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:

for other My-article-city.com Privacy Matters feel free to Contact My-article-city.com
